欢迎来到威廉斯堡餐厅颁奖典礼
Welcome to the Williamsburg Diner Awards Night!
这位是主持人 尼尔·帕特里克·哈哈哈
And here's your host, Neil Patrick Hairless!
今夜是大家这一年来
This is the night where everyone is recognized
所谓的"努力工作" 受到认可的夜晚
for their, well... let's call it work.
阿憨 西装挺好看
Nice suit, Han.
我好爱你在《马达加斯加的企鹅》里的演出
I loved you in The Penguins of Madagascar.
颁奖开始 首先
Here we go. The award for
最佳迟到烂理由奖得主是...
Worst Excuse for Being Late to Work goes to...
厄尔 作品是"我死了"
Earl, for: "I died."
这是真的
It was true.
我有足足六十秒算是真死了
I was dead for a full 60 seconds.
而最佳外语片得主是...
And the Foreign Film Award goes to...
奥列格 因为你总是满身外来细菌
Oleg, for always being covered in a foreign film.
是的 我想感谢好多助我得奖的外来细菌
Yeah. I have so many bacteria to thank...
但我要特别感谢链球菌
but a special shout-out to streptococcus!
而最佳骗小费骗子奖的得主是...
And the winner for Best Lie Told to Get a Bigger Tip goes to...
闺蜜 祝你好运
Good luck, girl.
跟你一起提名竞争这个奖真得很荣幸
It's an honor to share this category with you.
是麦克斯
It's Max...
得奖原因是常让客人看
for showing customers pictures
自己三个嗷嗷待哺小孩的照片
of her three small children on a regular basis.
这个奖我想献给我生命中的光
This award is dedicated to the lights of my life--
麦克欣 麦克斯二世
Maxine, Max Jr.,
与麦克"魏生津"
and Maxi-Pad.
我知道你们三个里只有一个能看与听到我
I know only one of you can see and hear me,
所以帮我跟另外两个说
so please tell the others
我 爱 你
I...love...you.
而最佳女服务员奖得奖人是
And the award for Best Waitress goes to...
可别是我
It better not!
卡洛琳
Caroline!
不要
No!
看来这是真的 女人只有
Well, I guess it's true-- women only win awards
演出丢人角色才会得奖
when they take on roles that are humiliating.
最佳动画"短"片得主是李憨
And the Best Animated Short goes to Han Lee!
这是菜单
Here's your menu.
我现在去帮你拿杯水
I'll be right back with your water
以及洗胃器
and a stomach pump.
不用菜单 我知道我自己要啥
Keep it. I know what I want.
我也知道我自己要啥
Me too. But it just seems like
但泰勒·斯威夫特就是死不分手
Taylor Swift is never going away.
你很搞笑
You're funny. Yeah.
但是我没心情看你搞笑
I'm not in the mood for funny.
我要番茄汤 家常沙拉多加面包丁
I will take tomato soup, house salad, extra croutons.
如果你那两颗"馒头"下没有人性
And you can charge me extra...
你可以收我额外面包丁的钱
if you have no heart behind those gazongas.
算啦 那边吧台有个男人没牙
It's cool. The guy at the counter has no teeth,
你可以吃他的面包丁
so you can have his.
少点搞笑 多点沙拉可以吗
Less funny--more salad. Right?
让那边的金发妞给我上菜吧
Maybe the blonde one should bring it.
你想要那妞帮你上吗
Oh, you want her to bring it?
那先把你之后行程全取消吧
Maybe clear your calendar.
坐卡座的女士不喜欢我态度 指名要你
Uh, the lady in the booth doesn't like my attitude and wants you,
我想我真正想说的是
so I guess what I'm saying is
我果然还宝刀未老
I still got it!
等等 有客人点我 而且没有接着说
Wait, a customer asked for me and didn't follow it with,
"把经理叫过来说话"吗
"I'd also like to see the manager"?
这可是第一次呀
That's a first for me!
喂 金发妹
Yo, blondie!
面包丁
Croutons!
上菜 番茄汤 家常沙拉
Pick up. Tomato soup, house salad.
我这里还有D[二号]电池特卖
And I'm also running a special on D batteries.
如果都买了 我再送一份
Buy both, and I'll thrown in this bootleg copy
电影《坏老板2》盗版光盘
of Horrible Bosses II.
坏老板2矮子来了
Here comes Horrible Bosses Too Small.
需要来点电池好能持续走路与说话吗
Need some new batteries to keep walking and talking?
不 我不像你 动力来自双D电池[胸]
No, Max, I'm not powered by double Ds like you.
同意
Preach.
别跟这货买电池
Don't buy batteries from that guy
除非你想心脏[起搏器]突然在公车上没电
unless you want your heart to stop on the bus.
奥列格 这份要多加面包丁
Oleg, this is supposed to have extra croutons.
这是我常客要的
It's for my regular.
是的 你没听错 我也有常客
Yeah, you heard me. It happened.
靠 加面包丁姐又来了吗
Oh, no, "extra croutons" is here again?
记得多收她钱
Make sure you charge her extra.
我又不是面包做的
I'm not made of stale bread!
当然不是 你是乐高积木做的 对吧
No, you're made of Legos, right?
我们不可以多收她钱
We are not charging her extra.
感觉她应该付不起
She looks like she can't afford it.
她要是付得起钱 她也不用来这吃了
If she could, why would she be eating here?
不要以貌取人
Well, don't judge a book by its cover.
像别人看到我 会觉得...
People look at me and--
觉得你床上一条虫吗
Think you're bad in bed?
你到底想说啥
What's your point?
我告诉你 我可不是床上一条虫
For your information, Max, I'm not bad in bed.
我在《模拟人生》界里 可是床上一条龙
In fact, I'm quite the stud in my Sims community.
你连在退休人士界里都只能算小蚯蚓
You wouldn't be a stud in a retirement community.
这是你的沙拉
Hi! Here's your salad...
五 六 七 八 九 十
Uh...five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
你继续说
Uh, continue.
我想跟你自我介绍一下
And I wanted to introduce myself.
我叫卡洛琳 是你的常驻服务员
I'm Caroline, you're regular waitress.
轮到我介绍啦 抱歉
Oh! My turn. Sorry.
我独居 我的植物都没你粘人
I live alone, and my plants aren't this needy.
我叫诺拉
I'm Nola.
这位是麦克斯 麦克斯 这是诺拉
And this is Max. Max, this is Nola.
哟 萝拉
'Sup, Lola?
是诺拉
It's Nola.
你看 这就是为啥我喜欢金发妹
See, this is why I like the blonde one.
她会用心听
She listens.
我能点个芝士蛋糕吗
May I please have a cheesecake?
没问题 也谢谢你 诺拉
Sure. And thank you, Nola.
我也觉得用心听别人说话很重要
I think it's important to listen to people.
樱桃派马上就到
Coming right back with that cherry pie.
她要是哪天不听人说话了我会跟她说
I'll tell her if she ever stops listening.
我觉得诺拉知道我不只是个服务生
I think Nola knows I'm more than just a waitress.
她能看穿这制服下的我
She can see right through this uniform.
我也能"看穿" 只要灯光对了就行
And so can I... in just the right light.
-关门 -我的天啊
- Close the door! - Oh, my God!
苏菲 我要被你吓死
Sophie, you scared me!
你还知道怕吗
You're scared?
我刚刚看到这牛奶的过期日才怕
I just saw the expiration date on this milk!
快点关上 快
Come on, close it, quick!
我在这里面躲奥列格呢
I'm in here hiding from Oleg.
如果你想避开奥列格
If you wanna get away from Oleg,
只要躲到卖牙线的地方就行了
just go anywhere they sell floss.
我觉得奥列格在偷吃
I think that Oleg is cheating on me.
你看
Look.
天啊
Oh, God!
她现在要大咧咧直接"甩"出来了吗
Now she's gonna start whipping it out?
你看
Look...
他有另一只秘密手机
He has a second secret phone.
是一次"性电话"
It's a boner phone.
你是说"一次性"电话吧
You mean a burner phone.
半斤八两
Same thing.
苏菲 你怎么知道
Sophie, how do you know
他不是只是拿来打长途电话或...
he just doesn't use it for long distance or...
或是给我正在打过去的女人打电话吗
Or for the woman that I'm calling right now?
快开免提
Oh, put her on speaker.
反正我也没别的事干了 我在上班
I've nothing else to do. I'm at work.
谁 奥列格吗
Da? Oleg?
奥列格
Oleg?
你学奥列格也太烂了
That... is a terrible Oleg.
他口齿哪有这么清晰
He is not that articulate.
看 这老婊子
Hah! That old whore!
她说啥了
What did she say?
我听不懂
I have no idea!
我不会说俄文 不过...
I don't speak Russian, but...
但我懂"老婊语"
I do speak "Old whore."
你们说 他脑子到底哪有病
Tell me, what is his problem?
他家有我这样甜美可人又青春的佳人
He has a sweet, young filly like me at home
结果他还要出去
and he needs to go out
去帮这俄国老婊"松松土"
and plow some old Russian field?
我很想问你们三个在这里面干嘛
Well...I'd ask what you three are doing in here,
但任何答案
but it's never gonna top
都不会比我脑子里想得还给劲
what I'm imagining you're doing in here.
真不敢相信诺拉今晚没来
I can't believe Nola didn't come in tonight.
这就像我那个星巴克咖啡师一样
This is exactly what happened with my Starbucks barista guy.
前一秒 他还摆弄着香蕉来"暗示"我
One minute, he's suggestively arranging the bananas at me,
下一秒 他就倒地扑街
and then next minute, he's face-down,
死在一滩豆奶里
dead in a puddle of soy milk.
麦克斯 万一她出事了怎么办
Max, what if something happened to her?
那我们就有更多面包丁吃了
More croutons for us!
她有说"我们明天见"
She said, "I'll see you tomorrow."
这话根本没啥含义 只是种说法
That doesn't mean anything. It's just an expression like,
就像"员工一定得洗手"
"Employees must wash hands."
或像"这孩子是你的"一样
Or... or, "The baby is yours."
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
苏菲 只是你而已啊
Oh, Sophie, it's just you.
你个死穷鬼
You're poor!
现在咱们扯平了
And now we're even.
你们看 我又偷来了 奥列格人呢
Look, I stole it again. Where's Oleg?
我告诉你他不会在哪里
I'll tell you where he's not--
烹饪学校
Culinary school.
他在休息
He's on break.
这老婊要惨了
Oh, she's gonna be sorry!
没人可以插进苏菲跟她男人之间
Oh...no one comes between Sophie and her man.
除非是我们"付钱"请来的
You know...unless we pay them to.
我有几件事
Couple things--
问题一 咱们这里有人工作吗
A--does anyone ever work here?
卡洛琳 别瞎操心了 加面包丁姐没事
Caroline, stop worrying. Extra Croutons is fine.
她刚才打电话来叫了餐厅外卖
She just called to order some diner food to be delivered.
原来 她是想死在家啊
Oh! So she wants to die at home.
我说了我们不做外送
I said we don't do deliveries.
我跟她说你们俩连把食物
I told her you two can barely get the food
从窗口送到桌上都很勉强了
from the window to the tables!
麦克斯 我必需得来
Max, I had to stop by
帮诺拉把她的沙拉与面包丁送过来
and bring Nola her salad and croutons.
她现在算是我的头号粉丝呢
I mean, she's kind of my biggest fan right now.
的确 因为我理解无能[失去了我]
True...'cause you just lost me.
我知道你觉得这很神经病
I know you think this is crazy,
但是诺拉看我的眼神里有些特别之处
but there's something about the way Nola looks at me.
感觉她看到了我身上的一些东西
It's like she's seeing something in me.
这女人戴着两副眼镜
The woman wears two pairs of glasses.
对她来说 你只是个废话多的黄橘色模糊体
To her, you're just a chatty yellow and orange blur.
人家跟我说你不送货[没让人爽到]呢
I was told you didn't deliver.
谁说的 她的旧爱们吗
By who, her old boy friends?
你们俩是来杀我还是干嘛的吗
Are you two gonna kill me or something?
因为如果是
Because if you are,
那我想换一顶帽子再死
I would like to put on a different hat.
不不不 她是担心你
No, no, no. She got worried.
因为你是她第一个常客
See, you're her first regular.
而我只是来看戏的
I'm just here for the story.
我猜想这扇门后可能有些怪玩意
I figured there'd be something freaky behind this door
比如15.2米长的蟒蛇与快递小哥的残骸
like a 50-foot python and what's left of the UPS guy.
而厄尔是猜你其实是男人
And Earl guessed you were a man.
没有男人
No man.
只有我与我的"老妹妹"以及我的照片
No, just me in here with my vagina and my photographs.
原来你是个摄影师啊
Oh! You're a photographer?
我也喜欢摄影
I love photography!
而我喜欢个人隐私
And I love privacy.
而我喜欢大麻
And I love pot.
我还以为在轮着说呢
Oh, I thought we were going around.
来吧 你最好也进来
Come on. You better come in too.
一阴一阳 一话多一封嘴
You're the Yin to her Yap.
小心地上
Hey, careful where you step.
我找不到我第三副眼镜
I can't find my third pair of glasses.
在你的帽子上啊
It's on top of your hat.
不 那是我的第四副
No, that's my fourth pair.
这是流浪比利
This is Billy the bum!
他以前住在我公寓街角的一个箱子里
He used to live in a box around the corner from my apartment.
他有一次还让我借住他家呢
He even let me stay over once
当时我想远离我那个烂室友一阵
when I had to get away from this bad roommate.
我之前那个吗
Oh, the one before me?
不 就是你
No, it was you.
你们俩在一起可真够闹腾
You two are a riot together.
你们让我想起我与我的摄影师老朋友
You remind me of me and my old photographer friend
安妮·莱柏维兹
Annie Leibovitz.
当然 这是在她...
Course, this was before...
在她成名之前吗
Before she got famous?
不 在她泡我之前
No. Before she hit on me.
我告诉她我对女人没兴趣
I told her I wasn't into girls.
可能她以为我戴这帽子所以是拉拉吧
But...I think she was confused by the derby.
是的 我觉得大家都这么误会了
Yeah. I think we're all a little confused by it.
诺拉 我很想问你是否功成名就过
Nola, I want to ask you if you've ever had any success,
但我不知道怎么问你才不会侮辱到你
but I don't know how to do that without insulting you.
没错 你不知道
That's correct. You don't.
你在苏活区要办摄影展啊
Oh! You're having a gallery show in SoHo?
慢走不送
Good-bye.
谢谢你们俩这么好心
Uh, it was nice of you two
过来... 看看我
to, uh, come over, check on me.
有点怪 不过很有心
Uh...weird, but nice.
或许我们可以去参加开幕啊
Perhaps we could come to the opening.
不用 你们不用这样
Oh. Oh, you don't need to do that.
我知道我们不用这样
I know we don't need to,
但或许我很想支持你以及你的杰出作品啊
but maybe I want to support you and your amazing work.
而麦克斯也会很享受免费酒水
And Max would enjoy. The free wine.
我会的
Yes, I would.
不
No.
我绝对会
Oh, I would.
不的意思是"不 别来"
No as in, "No, don't come."
抱歉 麻烦你们给点空间
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我想吃我的面包丁了
I wanna eat my croutons
不用两位滑稽歌舞演员相伴
without the vaudeville stylings
搞笑精与多管闲事精
of Shecky and Nosy.
给
Here.
太好了 我正在找这个呢
Oh, yeah, good. I was looking for this.
真不敢相信你为了一个餐厅常客这么上心
I can't believe you're doing all this for a diner regular.
好久没见你这么没节操上杆子倒贴了
I haven't seen you this desperate since Monday,
打从这周一二三四和周五之后
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday.
是啊 到周末时我已经放弃了
I know--on the weekends, I just give up.
瞧这主题
Look that title!
"下层社会"[未清洗的大物]
"The Great Unwashed."
奥列格的蛋蛋也参展了吗
Are Oleg's balls here?
麦克斯 这里是"艺术展"
Max, it's the "Art scene."
有点档次 至少说"睾丸"好吗
Class it up. At least say testicles.
晚上好 女士们
Evening, ladies.
厄尔 你怎么会在这里
Earl, what are you doing here?
阿憨 你的头要被毛衣吃掉了
And, Han, your sweater's eating your head.
我是来喝免费香槟的
I'm here for the champagne
还因为我找不到出去的路了
and because I couldn't find my way out.
我刚撞上了一张门的照片
I just walked into a picture of a door.
这里有的照片要卖到好几千美元
Some of these are going for thousands of dollars!
那个贱人诺拉真有钱 我猜她肯定
That Nola bitch is rich, and I bet she has
他妈的有度假屋 全靠蹭我面包丁挣得
a frigging summer house made out of my free croutons!
阿憨 这里是艺术展 要有格调
Han, it's the art scene. Class it up.
好歹也用"他妹的" 还有记得是"睾丸"哟
At least say "Freaking." Also, "Testicles."
我才不要把我的新高领毛衣浪费在你俩身上
Well, I'm not wasting this new turtleneck on you two.
我要去猎艳
I'm going to go mingle.
刚才一位高街时尚模特对我抛媚眼呢
A high fashion model was giving me the eye.
那她一定是喝"高"了吧
Then she'd have to be high.
阿憨 我还是待在这里吧
Uh, Han, I believe I'll stay here.
让忍者神龟当泡妞搭档
Nobody wins with a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle
想成功都难
as a wingman.
各位好呀
Oh, hey, everybody.
苏菲 奥列格
Hey, Sophie. Hey, Oleg.
我的档次可以降档了吗
So can I class it back down now?
抱歉我们来晚了 我刚在那边
Sorry we're late. I was just over there
欣赏一张拍摄桥下幸福情侣的照片
admiring the photo of the happy couple under the bridge.
幸福的情侣
Happy couple?
苏菲 那是两个瘾君子在共用一根针头
Sophie, they're two junkies sharing a needle.
是啊 至少那个女瘾君子
Yeah, well, at least the lady junkie
知道自己男人的"针头"碰过哪里
knows where his needle's been.
我觉得那女的连那男的名字都不知道
I don't even think she knows her name.
她只是假装不知道罢了
Well, she knows more than she's letting on.
其实她洞悉一切
She knows everything.
你们俩已经转过一圈了
Hey, you guys have been here a while.
哪里是偷食物的最佳去处
Where's the best place to steal some food?
麦克斯
Max!
抱歉 失礼了
Sorry, sorry.
要有档次地说 "睾"些食物
Classing it up: Testicles some food?
麦克斯 从你无礼的举止我可以看出
Oh, Max, I can tell by your sassy demeanor
你肯定还没看见你的照片
you haven't seen your photo yet.
什么照片 我从未用过空头支票在这行骗啊
What photo? I haven't bounced any checks here.
好吧 还真是我
Yep, that's me, all right.
我认出了"老娘懒得鸟"式撅嘴
I recognize that "I don't care" pout
以及沾在我头发上的千岛酱
and the Thousand Island dressing in my hair.
麦克斯 你的照片挂在墙上
Max, just because you're hanging on a wall
跟这个城市最贫穷最迷惘的灵魂们在一起
among the poorest, most lost souls in our city
并不意味着你的人生是...
doesn't mean that your life is...
我的照片就挂在我身后 是吗
I'm hanging right behind me, aren't I?
我的老天
Oh, my God!
不是正面全裸照 不幸中之万幸啊
It could be worse. You could be naked.
我穿着聚酯纤维衣服呢
This is worse than being naked!
这比不穿衣服还悲哀
I'm wearing polyester!
我在布鲁克林当服务员已经够悲哀了
It's bad enough I'm a waitress in Brooklyn.
现在我出现在曼哈顿 却还是服务员
Now I'm a waitress in Manhattan,
而这些家伙连小费都不给
and these guys didn't even tip!
别生气嘛 这只是一张照片
No, no, no, it's a photograph,
只是比较象征性意味吧
so it's more symbolic.
照片名就叫"服务员"
It's called "Waitress"
我还拿着记单本
and I'm holding a check pad.
这些蓝点点是什么意思
What do all these blue dots mean?
我的照片有问题吗
Is my picture in trouble?
这是有多少人次买你的照片的意思
That's how many times your print has been purchased.
这边 麦克斯 我们要远离
Over here, Max, away from that
那个穿着服务员制服的可悲金发女
pathetic blonde lady in the waitress uniform.
你别神经兮兮的好吗 根本没人认出你
Will you relax? No one even recognized you.
没人吗 刚才那个艺术评论家说
No one? What about that art critic who said that
"照片上我的笑容
"My smile on the photo
是对无望无出路的人生仍怀抱
was a study of tragic, foolish optimism
可悲盲目的乐观的绝佳案例"
in a hopeless, dead-end life"?
他呀
Oh, him.
"无望无出路的人生"
"Hopeless, dead-end life"?
更悲哀的是 没人买我的照片
And then worse, no one buys me?
就连作为一个失败者 都不能获得成功
I'm not even a success as a failure?
你完全是一个成功的失败者
You're totally a success as a failure.
那为什么我没有蓝点点 麦克斯
Then where are all the blue dots, Max?
有15个人买你耶
15 people bought you.
不管你要干嘛 千万别转身
Whatever you do, don't turn around.
瞧瞧这些蓝点点
Look at these dots!
我要跟这些人回家了
I am going home with all these people--
无论男女 无论黑人白人
men, women, black, white.
就像上世纪70年代乔·纳马斯家的换妻游戏那样
It's like a key party at Joe Namath's house in the '70s.
搞笑妹
Hey, Shecky!
你为什么要把蓝点贴到你朋友照片那里
Why are you putting a dot by your friend's photo?
卖这些照片应该能挣贼多钱吧
Uh, how many extra croutons can you buy
这么多钱你能付得起多少额外面包丁呢
with the buttload of money you're making from these photos?
贼多
A buttload.
好好 我懂 你不爽嘛
Okay, Okay. I get it, you're mad.
那我告诉你
Tell you what.
我免费送你一张你的照片
I will give you a free print of your photo.
听着 我不要照片
Look, keep the photo.
我不要我在"联姻"番茄酱的照片
I don't want a picture of me marrying ketchups.
我不要我跟任何人联姻的照片
I don't want a picture of me marrying anybody.
但你可以用其他方式补偿我
But you can pay me back another way.
我告诉过你 我不是同性恋
I told you, I'm not a lesbian.
我只是爱戴帽子而已
I just wear hats.
你的朋友说你不喜欢自己的照片
Your friend says you hate your photo.
不啊
No.
我喜欢被人偷拍
I enjoy being secretly photographed
尤其是在为某人偷加再偷加面包丁时
while I'm stealing someone extra, extra croutons.
我要申明一点
For the record,
我从来不觉得你的笑容很傻
I never saw your smile as foolish.
我觉得...
I saw it as, uh...
你笑得有点开
just a little big.
我只是想夸夸你啊
Uh--I'm trying to pay you a compliment.
不好意思 夸马腿上了
Well, you failed.
一直以来 每次你看着我
All this time, when you looked at me,
我以为你看到的是我的特别
I thought you saw something special,
但你真正看到的只是跟顾客介绍特别菜的人
but all you really saw was someone reading the specials.
我有个问题想问你
I have a question for you.
好吧 我戴圆顶礼帽
Okay, fine. I wear the derby
是因为我有一点小秃顶
because I have a little bit of a bald spot.
为什么没人买我
Why didn't I sell?
照片没拍好
The picture sucks.
我最差的作品之一
One of my worst.
如果你还想着要夸夸我
If you're still trying to give me a compliment,
那你真得加把劲儿了
you're still failing.
优秀的摄影师能捕捉到真实的瞬间
Look, a good photograph captures the truth.
我猜是因为没有人相信
And I guess no one really believes
你是一个服务员
you as a waitress.
这是我听过别人夸我最棒的话了
That is the single nicest thing anyone's ever said to me.
那不是你想要成为的人 我懂
So it's not where you wanna be--I get it.
我花了50年的时间才成为了今天的自己
Look, it's taken me 50 years to be where I am.
你还非常年轻
And you are still so young.
这是我听过别人夸我第二棒的话
That is the second-nicest thing anyone's ever said to me!
人生路还漫长 相信我
The road is long, and trust me,
这一路你会历尽艰辛
it can be really hard.
所以不管你做什么
So whatever you do,
请留住你脸上那充满希望的傻笑
you hold on to that foolishly hopeful smile.
还有...你那个搞笑的朋友
And...your funny friend.
好吗
Yes?
好的
Yes.
各位 今晚我们一同见证了
Uh, everyone, tonight we are witness
诺拉·安德兹
to the amazing work
非凡的作品
of Nola Anderz.
我建议站在这里的所有人 安静片刻
Why don't we all just stand here quietly for a moment
让诺拉的大作说明一切
and let Nola's pictures speak.
我的手机响了 在哪儿呢
That's my phone. Where is it?
宝贝 为什么我的手机会在你奶罩里
Baby, why is my phone in your bra?
别说话
Shh, please!
这是你的秘密手机 我都知道了
It's your secret phone! I know all about it.
你拿走了 快还给我
You took it? Give it to me.
她是谁 奥列格 那个下贱的老婊子是谁
Who is she, Oleg? Who is this skanky old whore?
保安 保安
Security! Security!
别别别 住手 是她拿了我手机
What--no, no, no! Stop, stop--she has my phone.
各位 那是他的手"鸡"
It's his boner phone, everybody!
那是他的手"鸡"
It's his boner phone!
而你居然有"睾"[胆]认为
And you had the testicles to think
是我会让你丢脸
I was gonna embarrass you.
苏菲
Hey, Sophie.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
你们听见了吗
Did you hear that?
这声音有点像...我也不知道
It sounds a little bit like...I don't know.
偷情之声
The sound of cheating.
你们俩还没和好吗
You guys haven't made up yet?
千万别在这里"合"
Don't make up here.
没呢 我昨晚睡在沙发上
No. I slept on the couch.
我超级想她 于是我一边看爱情喜剧
I missed her so much, I watched a romcom
一边吃了一整盒她的可食用内衣
while eating a whole box of her edible underwear.
还是不愿意跟我说话吗 苏菲
Still not talking to me, Sophie?
我再说最后一次 我真的没有其他女人
For the last time, there's nobody else but you.
我用那个手机
I use that phone...
干嘛
Yes?
用来...
to...
继续说啊
Go on.
我用它来打电话给...
I use it to call...
快说重点
Cut to the chase!
我妈
My mother.
他真是谁都不放过呀
Is there no one he won't sleep with?
我没告诉你是因为
I didn't tell you because
我不想让你觉得我是依恋妈妈的男人
I didn't want you to think I was a mama's boy.
除了我们玩"母子游戏"的时候
Except when we play "Mama and Boy."
好吧
Well...
我要说的话就跟我对
I'll tell you what I told that girl
扬基蜡烛店那女孩说的一样
at the Yankee Candle store.
"老娘不买[信]"
"I'm not buyin' it!"
我没骗你 苏菲
It's true, Sophie.
我在担心...我的头发会掉光
I'm afraid I'm... losing my hair.
奥列格
Oh...Oleg.
可你不知道吗
But don't you know...
就算你的头发
I mean, you could be balder than
比15年前杰里米·皮文还少
Jeremy Piven was 15 years ago,
我也依然爱你
and I'd still love ya.
我的手机呢
Where's my--
被发现了
Busted.
卡洛琳 我有东西要给你
Caroline, I have something for you.
我才不要又在一张
I'm not signing another one of those
巨大的生日卡片上签名
giant birthday cards again.
是我的照片
It's my picture.
这下可好 我有两个不服务客人的你
Great. Now I have two of you that don't wait on tables.
"谢谢你的面包丁 诺拉"
"Thanks for the croutons. Nola."
麦克斯 我们要把我挂在哪里呢
Max, where are we gonna hang me?
或许你应该在厕所里自挂东南枝
Maybe you should hang yourself in the bathroom
就像三年前我以为你会这么做那样
like I thought you would three years ago.
是啊 那次打赌害我输了20块
Yep. I lost $20 on that bet.
麦克斯
You know, Max,
或许我应该不再逃避这部分的人生
maybe I have to stop running away from this part of my life
而是拥抱它
and embrace it,
把它看作我人生的一段旅途
see it as part of my journey,
我美丽又激动人心的旅途
my...beautiful, exciting journey.
如果你再不闭嘴 我就在这里把你"挂"了
If you don't shut up, I'm gonna hang you right here.